[music]
All right.
Um,
so Minnesota short week. Uh, these guys
have won three in a row. Um, finding
ways to win, you know, uh, playing
really good defense and, uh, you know,
controlling the ball over there
offensively. Uh, a little more ground
and pound and play action. uh you know
so got our hands full but uh it's what
we're charged with you know next one up
>> playing an opponent a second time um
what's the point of emphasis when you
look at that first game and and and the
loss there what what's the thing that
that's top of your list of this is what
we have to do better to beat this team
this time around
>> well I mean we there was uh you know we
had some penalties that killed us we had
uh a lot of mas and we turned the ball
over um had a block field goal, you
know. Uh so there there was a number of
things we did in that game that uh you
know that were self-induced, you know,
so we got to be really disciplined. You
know, play disciplined football on the
road. It's going to be loud there. Um
and the things we can control, we have
to control them, you know, let's take
care of that and uh and then we can play
Minnesota. Colin Brown was uh was listed
as a nonparticipant on your your injury
report today with the knee. How serious
is that that thing?
>> Uh not sure. I mean, I'm not uh you
know, we'll we'll know more a little bit
later, but this is just something that
just uh just popped up when he came in
today. So hopeful this is uh something,
you know, just some type of irritation
from the game. Uh that's what I'm
hoping, but I'll I'll know more later.
I'll know more tonight.
>> Regarding the uh the ground game
yesterday, Dan, uh you abandoned it late
for obvious reasons, but when you went
back and looked at the tape, um
schematics, execution, why wasn't it
clicking for you guys yesterday?
>> Yeah, there was a couple of them that
were uh you know, schematically, uh you
know, didn't give our guys a chance
there. You know, one of them got you
know, they run it down backside. Uh
can't get away from that one. Um
you know, and then just, you know, it
was an execution. Uh and and we just
kind of took our turns with uh with you
know with how that went. Uh it was and
as you guys know I think you know it
takes really all 11 guys to get the run
game going. You know uh everybody's got
to be on par. So um you know one time
it's it's one player here whether it's
in the O line or um or at another spot.
It's not just there. you know, the backs
are involved, receivers, tight ends. So,
we just kind of took turns with uh
whether it was some of the combinations
or not, you know, we're not honoring the
ID or maybe it's not the right read. Um
but yeah, we had a there was a couple in
there. You know, I wish I could have had
the calls back, couple of calls back.
>> Curious with with Christian, um he was
limping pretty fiercely in the the
locker room after he's, you know, still
trying clearly to get past some the pain
hurdles there. you you've let a few
players um you know kind of play through
and and give you the heads up. Terion
being an example, Davenport still kind
of banged up, you know, when what goes
into the decision there where where a
guy is you maybe not 100% um you know
there is maybe a risk of something going
south like it did with Terion like how
how do you balance you know player want
to fight through it and protecting them
from themselves?
>> Yeah. Well, I think it's the type of
injury, you know, it's what what is that
and can it get worse, significantly
worse? Like, of course, there's a chance
for it to to feel worse, but is it
structurally are we are we talking about
something that's going to be a career
ender if we keep playing? Well, that's
totally different. Uh, but the things
where um, you know, it it's not going to
have that type of effect. Um, doesn't
mean it won't feel good, but you you
feel ready to go. Uh, I'm hearing from
everybody that you're you're healed.
You're 100% healed. And now it's just
about getting your feet back under. You
just got to play. They've done all they
can do and all you can do now is play
the game. And that's that's the best
thing for you to get you back. So, as
long as we check the box and all those,
um, we we try to make it go.
>> D, we obviously uh we know the
secondary's had some injuries, but how
do you explain the way the defense has
played over these last five games with a
relatively healthy front seven? Yeah,
we're just uh look, it's as you guys
know, the rushing coverage always go
together and we have not worked in
unison at, you know,
for for a number of plays, you know. I
mean, we we've gotten hit on on we've
gotten hit on a number of plays and uh
so, you know, some of that is,
you know, we play a certain style,
right?
>> [clears throat]
>> And then if if you feel like you're
you're not executing there, then you try
to get some help in areas. Well, I kind
of mentioned this last week. When you do
that, then you expose yourself and
others. And that happened a little bit
yesterday. You know, we try to play with
a lighter box. Um you know, and um and
then we got hit in the run game. Um some
of them we missed some tackles that
showed up. Uh where we fit, who the
support player is, that showed. And uh
you know it's obviously it's too much
man. It's not sustainable but um listen
you you live and you learn and uh you
know we've had some young guys that that
are getting valuable reps right now and
uh they they're going to learn from them
and grow from them.
>> Dan, there were a lot of comments
yesterday after the game from players
and I believe you even kind of alluded
it alluded to it yourself about we've
maybe lost our identity a little bit. Is
that a resiliency thing? Is that a
coaching thing? Is that a mentality
thing? Where and how can you work on
getting that back?
>> Yeah. Well, I'm always going to put that
on myself. I'm the head coach, so I
think that comes for me.
>> Big stock of the season. You know, they
look back at that the loss to Minnesota
as a as a demarcation point for this
year. I mean, do do you buy into the
fact that a game one game can change the
course of a season?
>> Um, not necessarily. I mean, we there
was other games that that, you know,
that we were in that that we weren't
able to to get a grasp of, you know, I
mean, um, you know, we had opportunities
to get back in that Philly game and we
we couldn't close. We were down in the
red zone and and, uh, defense got us the
ball back there and we weren't able to
do anything with it. Um, you know, now
certainly we did a number of things
wrong against Minnesota game one. I
mean, we everything you can do wrong in
all three phases, we did them and then
some. Um, you know, so that was that was
probably collectively our worst game
that we've played of the season and we
we were everybody had a a a hand in that
uh significant hand in that. So, um, no,
I mean, you you don't want those to
happen, but it happened, you know, and
then at some point you got to find a way
to make up for it in another, you know,
in another one of those games.
a lot of management at the end of the
the first half just kind of in general.
You know, I've heard from people that
that's like the trickiest thing to
manage just right you keeping it and
keeping it away from other teams and you
guys had a situation yesterday where you
you sort of ran an extra play before the
two-minute and then that that left them
a little bit of time um on the back end.
Just philosophically, what are you
trying to do there and and any you know
thing you do different about
yesterday's? Yeah, I mean it's it's hard
cuz I just told the guys I I told golf
to tell them to stay in bounds, you
know, and uh but then you're sitting
there and you feel like you you have a
real good feeling of what you're about
to get coverage wise and you like the
play that you got. So, it's hard not to
take the shot and uh golf made a hell of
a throw Tesla, you know, it's a hell of
a play, hell of a catch. And so yeah, I
mean ideally um man, if you could have
both um and so you do you weigh it and
uh chose to go for the shot and you know
and left a little bit of time out there.
>> How about the one right before the
two-minute like could could you have
taken that play that third down play and
run that after the two-minute, you know,
to waste 40 more seconds there?
>> Yeah, sure. Sure. I think we could have
done that, you know, could have done
that.
>> Dan,
>> Kingsley yesterday making us first
start. just what what did you think
about him when you watch a film back?
>> I thought it was really encouraging. I I
really did. I mean, for for his first
game to go out there, I thought uh man,
I thought he competed. I thought he
fought. Uh I thought he played fast. Um
it was it was very encouraging.
>> And Dan, your team is
>> your team has been built on kind of
controlling the trenches for a number of
years now, and that slipped down for the
past couple games. playoffs are not just
how important is it to kind of reseize
control of that part of the game over
these final two games? Reimpose
yourselves, I guess.
>> Yeah, it's vital. It's vital. Um because
it it's extremely difficult to control
anything if you can't control the run
game. The pass game is one thing, you
know, and nobody likes that either, but
uh you know, if we can't if we can't get
the run game in our favor, it becomes
very very difficult.
What what was your message to the team
today?
>> Uh move forward. You know, we we got
three days here uh of practice for these
guys to to get the mental work to
recover. Um you know, make sure they get
rest when they leave here and uh and get
back to work. And you know, nobody's
going to feel sorry for us. Nobody
cares. Um we got a we got a game plan
ready for them. they they uh they got to
go out there and and digest it as fast
as they can and be ready to go, man.
Emotionally, uh psychologically,
physically by the time Thursday hits.
That's the message.
>> I I just wanted to kind of follow up.
Perhaps I didn't ask my question in a
thorough enough manner. Do you feel like
there's a way with just two games left
that you can talk about the identity?
How does how do you reclaim that a
little bit to Will's point of kind of
reinforcing your will in the run game
and and winning in the trenches those
places that you were previously so
strong and that was your identity? How
can you get it back with just two games
to go?
>> I think you just do it.
You just do it.
Thanks guys.
>> Thanks D.
[music]
>> [music]
>> Hey, hey,
[music]
hey.